var questions = [{
	"question": "Which one of these toys made its debut in the 80s?",
	"option1": "G.I. Joe",
	"option2": "Troll Doll",
	"option3": "Strawberry Shortcake",
	"option4": "Processor",
	"answer": "Strawberry Shortcake"
}, {
	"question": "During the 80s, everyone wanted a pair of Ray-Ban sunglasses. What film helped to start this trend?",
	"option1": "Top Gun",
	"option2": "Lethal Weapon",
	"option3": "The Godfather",
	"option4": "Dirty Harry",
	"answer": "Top Gun"
}, {
	"question": "Who played the iconic character J.R. on the TV show Dallas?",
	"option1": "Patrick Duffy",
	"option2": "Howard Keel",
	"option3": "Larry Hagman",
	"option4": "Jim Davis",
	"answer": "Larry Hagman"
}, {
	"question": "In the 80s, Nintendo released their NES or Nintendo Entertainment System. What game came with the system?",
	"option1": "Breakout",
	"option2": "Super Mario Bros.",
	"option3": "Frogger",
	"option4": "Tetris",
	"answer": "Super Mario Bros."
}, {
	"question": "What men's hairstyle was trendy in the 80s?",
	"option1": "The Mullet",
	"option2": "The Crop",
	"option3": "Mop Top",
	"option4": "The flip",
	"answer": "The Mullet"
}, {
	"question": "What was the highest grossing movie of the 1980s?",
	"option1": " Kramer Vs. Kramer",
	"option2": "E.T.",
	"option3": "Jaws",
	"option4": "Rocky",
	"answer": "E.T."
}, {
	"question": "In the 80s, Bruce Willis played which of these characters?",
	"option1": "John Hancock",
	"option2": "John McClane",
	"option3": "Martin Riggs",
	"option4": "Robert Neville",
	"answer": "John McClane"
}, {
	"question": "Which of these video games was not introduced in the 1980s?",
	"option1": "Frogger",
	"option2": "Digger",
	"option3": "Snake",
	"option4": "Pac-Man",
	"answer": "Snake"
}, {
	"question": "Care Bears were all the rage during the 80s. Which Care Bear was green?",
	"option1": "Best Friend Bear",
	"option2": "Good Luck Bear",
	"option3": "Funshine Bear",
	"option4": "Birthday Bear",
	"answer": "Good Luck Bear"
}, {
	"question": "What 80s fashion trend was inspired by the movie Flashdance?",
	"option1": "Bell Bottoms",
	"option2": "Crocs",
	"option3": "Legwarmers",
	"option4": "Ear Muffs",
	"answer": "Legwarmers"
}];